import {FlashcardsData, SubCategory} from "../type/flash-card.type";

const baseUrl = 'https://home-page-api-34607.herokuapp.com/flash-cards';

export async function getFlashCards(): Promise<FlashcardsData> {
  try {
    const response = await fetch(baseUrl, {
      method: 'GET',
      headers: {
        'Content-Type': 'application/json'
      },
      cache: 'no-store',
    });

    return (await response.json()) as FlashcardsData;
  } catch (error) {
    console.log(error);
    return getLocalCards(error);
  }
}

function getLocalCards(error: any): Promise<FlashcardsData> {
  const subCategory1: SubCategory = {
    id: '1-1',
    name: '100 Words',
    flashCards:
      [
        {id: "1", question: "gastr-", answer: "Stomach", example: ""},
        {id: "2", question: "cardi-", answer: "Heart", example: ""},
        {id: "3", question: "megal-", answer: "Enlarged", example: ""},
        {id: "4", question: "-itis", answer: "Inflammation", example: ""},
        {id: "5", question: "dermat-", answer: "Skin", example: ""},
        {id: "6", question: "plast-", answer: "Surgical repair", example: ""},
        {id: "7", question: "cerebr-", answer: "Brain", example: ""},
        {id: "8", question: "path-", answer: "Disease", example: ""},
        {id: "9", question: "-ectomy", answer: "Surgical removal", example: ""},
        {id: "10", question: "enter-", answer: "Intestines", example: ""},
        {id: "11", question: "-osis", answer: "Any condition", example: ""},
        {id: "12", question: "-otomy", answer: "Cut into", example: ""},
        {id: "13", question: "aden-", answer: "gland", example: ""},
        {id: "14", question: "angi-", answer: "Vessel", example: ""},
        {id: "15", question: "-oma", answer: "Tumor", example: ""},
        {id: "16", question: "nephr-", answer: "Kidney", example: ""},
        {id: "17", question: "hepat-", answer: "Liver", example: ""},
        {id: "18", question: "arthr-", answer: "Joint", example: ""},
        {id: "19", question: "blephar-", answer: "eyelid", example: ""},
        {id: "20", question: "-ologist", answer: "Specialist", example: ""},
        {id: "21", question: "rhin-", answer: "Nose", example: ""},
        {id: "22", question: "gingiv-", answer: "gum", example: ""},
        {id: "23", question: "-malacia", answer: "Soft", example: ""},
        {id: "24", question: "-ology", answer: "The study of", example: ""},
        {id: "25", question: "Spasm", answer: "Involuntary contractions", example: ""},
        {id: "26", question: "-algia", answer: "pain", example: ""},
        {id: "27", question: "crani-", answer: "skull", example: ""},
        {id: "28", question: "end-", answer: "Inside, within", example: ""},
        {id: "29", question: "hemi-", answer: "half", example: ""},
        {id: "30", question: "-oid", answer: "like", example: ""},
        {id: "31", question: "hyper-", answer: "Above, more than normal", example: ""},
        {id: "32", question: "cyst-", answer: "Sac containing fluid", example: ""},
        {id: "33", question: "chole-", answer: "bile", example: ""},
        {id: "34", question: "hypo-", answer: "under", example: ""},
        {id: "35", question: "-scop-", answer: "observe", example: ""},
        {id: "36", question: "hyster-", answer: "uterus", example: ""},
        {id: "37", question: "-ostomy", answer: "Create an opening", example: ""},
        {id: "38", question: "para-", answer: "Beside, beyond", example: ""},
        {id: "39", question: "-lysis", answer: "Loosening, destruction", example: ""},
        {id: "40", question: "cervic-", answer: "neck", example: ""},
        {id: "41", question: "chondr-", answer: "cartilage", example: ""},
        {id: "42", question: "cyan-", answer: "blue", example: ""},
        {id: "43", question: "hem(at)-", answer: "blood", example: ""},
        {id: "44", question: "ost-", answer: "bone", example: ""},
        {id: "45", question: "psycho-", answer: "mind", example: ""},
        {id: "46", question: "lip-", answer: "fat", example: ""},
        {id: "47", question: "my-", answer: "muscle", example: ""},
        {id: "48", question: "lith-", answer: "stone", example: ""},
        {id: "49", question: "opthalm- opt-", answer: "Eye", example: ""},
        {id: "50", question: "proct-", answer: "Anus", example: ""},
        {id: "51", question: "cost-", answer: "Rib", example: ""},
        {id: "52", question: "-gram", answer: "Record", example: ""},
        {id: "53", question: "acro-", answer: "Extremities", example: ""},
        {id: "54", question: "rhexis", answer: "Break, burst", example: ""},
        {id: "55", question: "carcin-", answer: "Cancer", example: ""},
        {id: "56", question: "-penia", answer: "Decrease", example: ""},
        {id: "57", question: "gen-", answer: "Original, production", example: ""},
        {id: "58", question: "burso-", answer: "Sac", example: ""},
        {id: "59", question: "retr(o)-", answer: "Backwards", example: ""},
        {id: "60", question: "trip-", answer: "Rub, friction", example: ""},
        {id: "61", question: "strept-", answer: "Twist", example: ""},
        {id: "62", question: "-desis", answer: "Binding", example: ""},
        {id: "63", question: "mani-", answer: "Madness", example: ""},
        {id: "64", question: "glosso-", answer: "Tongue", example: ""},
        {id: "65", question: "-trophy", answer: "Development", example: ""},
        {id: "66", question: "supra-", answer: "Above", example: ""},
        {id: "67", question: "-ptosis", answer: "Falling", example: ""},
        {id: "68", question: "-dyn-", answer: "Pain", example: ""},
        {id: "69", question: "mast-", answer: "Breast", example: ""},
        {id: "70", question: "-rrhaphy", answer: "Suture", example: ""},
        {id: "71", question: "dent-", answer: "Teeth", example: ""},
        {id: "72", question: "cephal-", answer: "Head", example: ""},
        {id: "73", question: "auto-", answer: "Self", example: ""},
        {id: "74", question: "epi-", answer: "Upon", example: ""},
        {id: "75", question: "hydro-", answer: "Water", example: ""},
        {id: "76", question: "lobo-", answer: "Section", example: ""},
        {id: "77", question: "-emesis", answer: "Vomiting", example: ""},
        {id: "78", question: "contra-", answer: "Against, counter", example: ""},
        {id: "79", question: "-iasis", answer: "Condition", example: ""},
        {id: "80", question: "trans-", answer: "Through, across", example: ""},
        {id: "81", question: "brady-", answer: "Slow", example: ""},
        {id: "82", question: "-ectasis", answer: "Expansion", example: ""},
        {id: "83", question: "cyt-", answer: "Cell", example: ""},
        {id: "84", question: "odont-", answer: "Tooth", example: ""},
        {id: "85", question: "leuk-", answer: "White", example: ""},
        {id: "86", question: "-esthesia", answer: "Sensation", example: ""},
        {id: "87", question: "cantho-", answer: "Angle at the end of the eyelid", example: ""},
        {id: "88", question: "steno-", answer: "Narrow, contracted", example: ""},
        {id: "89", question: "cheil-", answer: "Lip", example: ""},
        {id: "90", question: "-cele", answer: "hernia", example: ""},
        {id: "91", question: "benign", answer: "Mild, not cancerous", example: ""},
        {id: "92", question: "semen", answer: "Seed", example: ""},
        {id: "93", question: "celio-", answer: "Abdomen", example: ""},
        {id: "94", question: "erythro-", answer: "Red", example: ""},
        {id: "95", question: "vaso-", answer: "Vessel", example: ""},
        {id: "96", question: "melan-", answer: "Black", example: ""},
        {id: "97", question: "cauda-", answer: "Tail", example: ""},
        {id: "98", question: "lingua-", answer: "Tongue", example: ""},
        {id: "99", question: "myring-", answer: "Eardrum", example: ""},
        {id: "100", question: "spondyl-", answer: "Spinal column", example: ""},
      ],
  };
  const subCategory2: SubCategory = {
    id: "1-2",
    name: "50 Abbreviations",
    flashCards: [
      { id: "1", question: "WBC", answer: "White Blood Cells" },
      { id: "2", question: "ENT", answer: "Ears Nose & Throat" },
      { id: "3", question: "AMA", answer: "American Medical Association" },
      { id: "4", question: "BP", answer: "Blood Pressure" },
      { id: "5", question: "dx", answer: "Diagnosis" },
      { id: "6", question: "RBC", answer: "Red Blood Cell" },
      { id: "7", question: "SOB", answer: "Shortness of Breath" },
      { id: "8", question: "WHO", answer: "World Health Organization" },
      { id: "9", question: "WNL", answer: "Within Normal Limits" },
      { id: "10", question: "OD", answer: "Overdose" },
      { id: "11", question: "CBC", answer: "Complete Blood Count" },
      { id: "12", question: "sx", answer: "Symptoms" },
      { id: "13", question: "bx", answer: "Biopsy" },
      { id: "14", question: "DM", answer: "Diabetes Mellitus" },
      { id: "15", question: "AKI", answer: "Acute Kidney Injury" },
      { id: "16", question: "CAD", answer: "Coronary Artery Disease" },
      { id: "17", question: "ASD", answer: "Atrial Septal Defect" },
      { id: "18", question: "COPD", answer: "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease" },
      { id: "19", question: "CVA", answer: "Cerebrovascular Accident" },
      { id: "20", question: "MI", answer: "Myocardial Infarction" },
      { id: "21", question: "OSA", answer: "Obstructive Sleep Apnea" },
      { id: "22", question: "TSH", answer: "Thyroid Stimulating Hormone" },
      { id: "23", question: "H&P", answer: "History & Physical" },
      { id: "24", question: "ROS", answer: "Review of Symptoms" },
      { id: "25", question: "ED", answer: "Emergency Department" },
      { id: "26", question: "ICU", answer: "Intensive Care Unit" },
      { id: "27", question: "CPT", answer: "Current Procedural Terminology" },
      { id: "28", question: "ICD", answer: "International Classification of Disease" },
      { id: "29", question: "OTC", answer: "Over the Counter" },
      { id: "30", question: "DJD", answer: "Degenerative Joint Disease" },
      { id: "31", question: "NSAID", answer: "Non-Steroidal Anti-Inflammatory Drugs" },
      { id: "32", question: "CHF", answer: "Congestive Heart Failure" },
      { id: "33", question: "TB", answer: "Tuberculosis" },
      { id: "34", question: "IUD", answer: "Intrauterine Device" },
      { id: "35", question: "LMP", answer: "Last Menstrual Period" },
      { id: "36", question: "TBSA", answer: "Total Body Surface Area" },
      { id: "37", question: "DVT", answer: "Deep Vein Thrombosis" },
      { id: "38", question: "PE", answer: "Pulmonary Embolism" },
      { id: "39", question: "TIA", answer: "Transient Ischemic Attack" },
      { id: "40", question: "CABG", answer: "Coronary Artery Bypass Graft" },
      { id: "41", question: "DDD", answer: "Degenerative Disc Disease" },
      { id: "42", question: "fx", answer: "Fracture" },
      { id: "43", question: "HTN", answer: "Hypertension" },
      { id: "44", question: "I&D", answer: "Incision and Drainage" },
      { id: "45", question: "IBS", answer: "Irritable Bowel Syndrome" },
      { id: "46", question: "IM", answer: "Intramuscular" },
      { id: "47", question: "PUD", answer: "Peptic Ulcer Disease" },
      { id: "48", question: "RA", answer: "Rheumatoid Arthritis" },
      { id: "49", question: "SQ", answer: "Subcutaneous" },
      { id: "50", question: "UTI", answer: "Urinary Tract Infection" }
    ]
  };
  const subCategory3: SubCategory = {
    id: '1-3',
    name: 'Terminology Prefixes',
    flashCards: [
      {id: '1', question: 'a-', answer: 'Without', example: 'Atypical'},
      {id: '2', question: 'ab-', answer: 'Away from', example: 'Abduction'},
      {id: '3', question: 'ad-', answer: 'Increase', example: 'Adduction'},
      {id: '4', question: 'ante-', answer: 'Before', example: 'Antepartum'},
      {id: '5', question: 'anti-', answer: 'Against', example: 'Antipsychotic'},
      {id: '6', question: 'an-', answer: 'Without', example: 'Anoxia'},
      {id: '7', question: 'apo-', answer: 'Off, away from', example: 'Apophysis'},
      {id: '8', question: 'auto-', answer: 'Self', example: 'Autograph'},
      {id: '9', question: 'bi-', answer: 'Two, Twice', example: 'Bilateral'},
      {id: '10', question: 'bin-', answer: 'Double', example: 'Binocular'},
      {id: '11', question: 'brady-', answer: 'Slow', example: 'Bradycardia'},
      {id: '12', question: 'cata-', answer: 'Downwards', example: 'Catabolism'},
      {id: '13', question: 'con-', answer: 'With', example: 'Congenital'},
      {id: '14', question: 'diplo-', answer: 'Double', example: 'Diplopia'},
      {id: '15', question: 'de-', answer: 'Down, Without', example: 'Dehydrate'},
      {id: '16', question: 'dia-', answer: 'Completely', example: 'Dialysis'},
      {id: '17', question: 'dys-', answer: 'Abnormal', example: 'Dysphagia'},
      {id: '18', question: 'ec-', answer: 'Outside', example: 'Ectoderm'},
      {id: '19', question: 'endo-', answer: 'Within, in', example: 'Endotracheal'},
      {id: '20', question: 'epi-', answer: 'On, Upon', example: 'Epidermis'},
      {id: '21', question: 'eu-', answer: 'Normal, Good', example: 'Eupnea'},
      {id: '22', question: 'ex-', answer: 'Outwards', example: 'Exostosis'},
      {id: '23', question: 'extra-', answer: 'Outside of', example: 'Extrapleural'},
      {id: '24', question: 'hemi-', answer: 'Half', example: 'Hemicolectomy'},
      {id: '25', question: 'hetero-', answer: 'Different', example: 'Heterograft'},
      {id: '26', question: 'homo-', answer: 'Same', example: 'Homoplasty'},
      {id: '27', question: 'hyper-', answer: 'Excessive', example: 'Hyperthyroidism'},
      {id: '28', question: 'hypo-', answer: 'Incomplete', example: 'Hypoglycemia'},
      {id: '29', question: 'in-', answer: 'Inward', example: 'Inhalation'},
      {id: '30', question: 'infra-', answer: 'Beneath', example: 'Infra-axillary'},
      {id: '31', question: 'inter-', answer: 'Between', example: 'Intercostals'},
      {id: '32', question: 'intra-', answer: 'Within, in', example: 'Intramuscular'},
      {id: '33', question: 'juxta-', answer: 'Near', example: 'Juxta-articular'},
      {id: '34', question: 'macro-', answer: 'Large, Long', example: 'Macrocephalus'},
      {id: '35', question: 'mal-', answer: 'Abnormal', example: 'Malformation'},
      {id: '36', question: 'mega-', answer: 'Great', example: 'Megacolon'},
      {id: '37', question: 'meta-', answer: 'Change', example: 'Metastasis'},
      {id: '38', question: 'micro-', answer: 'Small', example: 'Microscope'},
      {id: '39', question: 'mono-', answer: 'One', example: 'Monochromatic'},
      {id: '40', question: 'morpho-', answer: 'Shape', example: 'Morphology'},
      {id: '41', question: 'multi-', answer: 'Many', example: 'Multipara'},
      {id: '42', question: 'neo-', answer: 'New', example: 'Neonate'},
      {id: '43', question: 'nulli-', answer: 'None', example: 'Nulligravida'},
      {id: '44', question: 'pachy-', answer: 'Thick', example: 'Pachyderma'},
      {id: '45', question: 'pan-', answer: 'All, Total', example: 'Pancytopenia'},
      {id: '46', question: 'para-', answer: 'Beside', example: 'Parathyroid glands'},
      {id: '47', question: 'per-', answer: 'Through', example: 'Percutaneous'},
      {id: '48', question: 'peri-', answer: 'Surrounding', example: 'Periosteum'},
      {id: '49', question: 'poly-', answer: 'Many, Much', example: 'Polymyositis'},
    ]
  };
  const subCategory4: SubCategory = {
    id: "1-4",
    name: "Terminology Suffixes",
    flashCards: []
  };
  const subCategory5: SubCategory = {
    id: "1-5",
    name: "Word Terminals",
    flashCards: [
      {
        id: "1",
        question: "-ic, -tic",
        answer: "pertaining to; having to with",
        example: "hepatic, genetic, hypnotic",
        type: "adjective",
      },
      {
        id: "2",
        question: "-al",
        answer: "pertaining to; having to with",
        example: "dermal, bilateral",
        type: "adjective",
      },
      {
        id: "3",
        question: "-ac",
        answer: "pertaining to; having to with",
        example: "cardiac, celiac",
        type: "adjective",
      },
      {
        id: "4",
        question: "-ar",
        answer: "pertaining to; having to with",
        example: "ulnar, scapular, patellar",
        type: "adjective",
      },
      {
        id: "5",
        question: "-ular",
        answer: "pertaining to; having to with",
        example: "valvular, radicular",
        type: "adjective",
      },
      {
        id: "6",
        question: "-ary",
        answer: "pertaining to; having to with",
        example: "coronary, biliary",
        type: "adjective",
      },
      {
        id: "7",
        question: "-ical",
        answer: "pertaining to; having to with",
        example: "surgical, pharmaceutical",
        type: "adjective",
      },
      {
        id: "8",
        question: "-um",
        answer: "the thing being described by word element",
        example: "endothelium, labium, cerebrum",
        type: "noun",
      },
      {
        id: "9",
        question: "-is",
        answer: "the thing being described by word element",
        example: "dermis, pelvis",
        type: "noun",
      },
      {
        id: "10",
        question: "-us",
        answer: "the thing being described by word element",
        example: "umbilicus, thrombus",
        type: "noun",
      },
      {
        id: "11",
        question: "-a (singular)",
        answer: "the thing being described by word element",
        example: "bursa, gingiva, conjunctiva",
        type: "noun",
      },
      {
        id: "12",
        question: "-a (plural of -um or -on)",
        answer: "the thing being described by word element",
        example: "labia, endothelia",
        type: "noun",
      },
      {
        id: "13",
        question: "-ae (plural of -a or -um)",
        answer: "the thing being described by word element",
        example: "bursa, gingivae",
        type: "noun",
      },
      {
        id: "14",
        question: "-y",
        answer: "act of; result of; procedure",
        example: "endoscopy, microscopy",
        type: "noun",
      },
      {
        id: "15",
        question: "-ia",
        answer: "disease; condition",
        example: "amnesia, anosia, dysphagia",
        type: "noun",
      },
      {
        id: "16",
        question: "-ism",
        answer: "disease; condition",
        example: "alcoholism, autism, albinism",
        type: "noun",
      },
      {
        id: "17",
        question: "-ac",
        answer: "person affected by",
        example: "maniac, hemophiliac",
        type: "noun",
      },
      {
        id: "18",
        question: "-ate",
        answer: "to perform, bring about; put into action",
        example: "terminate, exfoliate, fixate",
        type: "verb",
      },
      {
        id: "19",
        question: "-tion",
        answer: "process, action, condition",
        example: "ablation, ligation, retraction",
        type: "noun",
      },
      {
        id: "20",
        question: "-esis",
        answer: "condition or process",
        example: "amniocentesis, uresis, electrophoresis",
        type: "noun",
      },
      {
        id: "21",
        question: "-id",
        answer: "to be; being",
        example: "rigid, flaccid, fluid, parotid, putrid",
        type: "adjective",
      },
    ]
  };

  return Promise.resolve({
    categories: [
      {
        id: '1',
        name: 'Medical Coding',
        subCategories: [
          subCategory1,
          subCategory2,
          subCategory3,
          subCategory4,
          subCategory5,
        ]
      },
      {
        id: '2',
        name: `${error}`,
        subCategories: []
      }
    ]
  });
}
